quiz_questions = [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        }
    ]